All aboard the ABC Train!
A for Apple, B for Ball,
C for Cat climbing up the wall!
D for Dog, E for Elephant gray,
F for Fish swimming away!
G, H, I, J, K and L,
Hear the shiny train whistle and bell!
Letter M is smiling bright,
Guiding the train into the light!
Chugga-chugga choo-choo, hear the bell ring,
Singing out our letters while we sing, sing, sing!
Riding down the track from A to Z,
Learning all the letters happily!
N for Nest, O for Owl so wise,
P for Panda with round black eyes!
Q, R, S, T, moving fast,
Watching all the pretty letters pass!
U, V, W, X, Y, Z, Now we know the letters, you and me!
Every letter has a friendly sound,
Spelling all the magic words around!
Chugga-chugga choo-choo, hear the bell ring,
Singing out our letters while we sing, sing, sing!
Riding down the track from A to Z,
Learning all the letters happily!
Next stop: Reading Station! Choo-choo! Ding-ding!